epiloglaser.com 2019-08-29

# Epilog Laser Privacy Policy

You have control over your data. If you have any questions, concerns, or requests regarding your data or personal information and how we use it, feel free to contact us at [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com).

## Table Of Contents

  * Introduction 
  * What Information Do We Collect? 
  * What are the Legal Bases for Our Collection and Use of Personal Information?
  * Who Collects Your Personal Information? 
  * How Do We Use the Information We Collect? 
  * What Information Do We Disclose to Third Parties?
  * Privacy Settings/Opt Out
  * Your Choices About Your Information
  * General
  * Geographic Location
  * Retention and Deletion
  * About Us

## Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

This privacy policy (“Policy”) is intended to inform users of the websites and products (collectively, the “Services”) provided by Epilog Corporation (“Epilog Laser”, “we”, or “us”) about how we gather and use personal information collected by us in connection with the Services. We will take reasonable steps to protect user privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this policy and with applicable U.S. laws. In this policy, “user” or “you” means any person using or otherwise benefitting from the Service or otherwise submitting personal information to Epilog Laser via the Services. BY SUBMITTING INFORMATION TO EPILOG LASER, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVAY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THE SERVICES.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

_Personal Information:_

We collect the personal information you submit to us, including your name, email address, street address, city, state/province, zip or postal code, country, company name, phone number, and the serial number of your product in order to communicate with you, send you the physical or digital items you requested, and possibly send you limited physical or digital informational communications.

_Other Personal Identifiers:_

Apart from the personal information described above, Epilog Laser does not collect and does not wish to receive any personally identifying information. Without limitation, you shall not submit to Epilog Laser any social security number, financial account number, credit or debit card number (other than the number of the card paying for the Services), driver’s license number or government ID number. Children under 13 years of age that use the Services are not permitted to provide or upload any personal information.

_Web Tracking Information:_

We, and our third party service providers, may use web tracking technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, and clear GIFs in order to operate the Services efficiently and to collect data related to usage of the Services. Such collected data (“Web Tracking Information”) may include the address of the websites you visited before and after you visited the Services, the type of browser you are using, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, what pages in the Services you visit, how long you visited pages, and what links you clicked on. In order to collect Web Tracking Information and to make your use of the Services more efficient, we may store cookies on your computer. We may also use web tracking technologies that are placed in web pages within the Services to collect information about actions that users take when they interact with the Services and Epilog Laser’s Contractors (as defined herein) may also do so. We do not correlate Web Tracking Information to individual user Personal Information, except for internal operational, product development, and administrative purposes of the Services. Some Web Tracking Information may include data, such as IP address data, that is unique to you. You may be able to modify your browser settings to alter which web tracking technologies are permitted when you use the Services, but this may affect the performance of the Services.

**What are the Legal Bases for Our Collection and Use of Personal Information?**

We rely on the following legal grounds to process your Personal Information:

  * Performance of a contract – we need to collect and use your Personal Information to perform our agreement with you to deliver the Services as described in this Privacy Policy
  * Consent – We may use or disclose some of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy subject to your consent.
  * Legitimate interests – We may use your Personal Information for our legitimate interests to improve our products and services and the Services. Consistent with our legitimate interests and any choices that we offer or consents that may be required under applicable laws, we may use technical information as described in this Privacy Policy

**Who Collects Your Personal Information?**

In some cases, Epilog Laser collects your Personal Information directly. In other cases, we rely on a third party service to handle the collection and temporary processing and storage of your Personal Information. The third party service we use for this purpose is Logiforms Software Inc., located in Vancouver, British Colombia, Canada.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

_Personal Information:_

Your Personal Information may be supplemented with additional information regarding your activities on the Service; to the extent that such information is linked specifically to you, we will treat that additional information as your Personal Information. We may use your email address to send you marketing materials about Epilog Laser and its products and services. We may also use Personal Information for the internal operation, product development, and administrative purposes of the Services.

_Web Tracking Information:_

We use Web Tracking Information to administer the Services and to understand how well our Services are working, to store your user preferences, and to develop statistical information on usage of the Services. This allows us to determine which features and content users like best to help us improve our Services, to personalize your user experience, and to measure overall effectiveness.

_Aggregate Information:_

We will also create statistical, aggregated data relating to our users and the Services for analytical purposes. Aggregated data is derived from Personal Information and Web Tracking Information, but its aggregated form it does not duplicate or reveal any Personal Information or relate to or identify any individual. This data is used to understand our customer base and to develop, improve, and market our services.

**What Information Do We Disclose to Third Parties?**

_Personal Information:_

We will not disclose your Personal Information to any third parties except as follows:

  * (i) to third party contractors engaged to provide services on our behalf (“Contractors”), such as performing marketing, analyzing data and usage of the Services, hosting and operating the Services or providing support and maintenance services for the Services, or providing customer service.
  * (ii) when we have your consent to share the information.

_Email Communications:_

If you provide us with your email address, we will send you administrative and promotional emails. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, you may do so by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the email, or by emailing your request to [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com).

_Web Tracking Information:_

We disclose Web Tracking Information to Contractors in order to analyze the performance of the Services and the behavior of users, and to operate and improve the Services.

_Aggregate Information:_

We may disclose aggregated data that does not contain Personal Information to any third parties, such as potential customers, business partners, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations.

_Network Operators:_

Use of the Services may involve use of the services of third party telecommunications carriers. Such carriers are not our contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of the Services is not “Personal Information” and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of telecommunications carriers.

_Legal Exception:_

Notwithstanding the above, we may in any event use Personal Information and other information collected through the Services to the extent required by lay or legal process, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements (including this Privacy Policy) with you, or if in our reasonable discretion use is necessary to protect our legal rights or to protect third parties.

_Additional Disclosures:_

We reserve the right to disclose any information we collect in connection with the Service, including Personal Information, (a) to any successor to our business as a result of any merger, acquisition, asset sale, or similar transaction; and (b) to any law enforcement, judicial authority, or governmental or regulatory authority, to the extent required by law or if in our reasonable discretion disclosure is necessary to enforce or protect our legal rights or to protect third parties.

_Distribution Partners:_

Epilog Laser operates in partnership with distributors around the world. In cases where we have a distribution partner located in your region, we may share your Personal Information with the distribution partner so that they can contact you and process your request. If you believe one of our distribution partners is mishandling or misusing your data, please let us know at [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com). You have the right to lodge a complaint against our distribution partners with a national Data Protection Authority; you can find out about the Data Protection Authority in your country here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

**Privacy Settings/Opt Out**

If you would like any or all of your Personal Information permanently removed from our database(s), please contact us at [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com) and we will promptly delete it. Aggregate Information derived from your Personal Information will be maintained and/or deleted in the ordinary course of Epilog Laser’s business.

**Your Choices About Your Information**

You have the right to:

  * request an accounting of all Personal Information that we possess that pertains to you in an electronically portable format (e.g., electronic copies of information attached to an email).
  * request that we change any Personal Information that pertains to you.
  * request that we delete any Personal Information that pertains to you.

To request an accounting of your Personal Information, a change to your Personal Information, or deletion of your Personal Information, contact [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com).

If you are a resident of the European Union and have a complaint about our use or processing of your Personal Information, you have a right to lodge a complaint with a national Data Protection Authority. Each European Union member nation has established its own Data Protection Authority; you can find out about the Data Protection Authority in your country here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>.

If you have consented to the collection, processing, and/or transfer of your Personal Information, you have the right fully or partially to withdraw your consent. To withdraw your consent, please contact [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com). Once we have received notification that you withdraw your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purposes to which you consented unless there are compelling legitimate grounds for further processing or for the establishment, exercise, or defense of legal claims.

**General**

_Security:_

We use reasonable security precautions to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Information in accordance with this policy and applicable law. However, no Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur. Without limitation of the foregoing, we are not responsible for the actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties that breach our reasonable security procedures.

_Links:_

The Epilog Laser Services may contain links to other websites as services. Epilog Laser is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our Services and review the privacy statements of each third party website. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Services.

_Amendments:_

Epilog Laser may modify or amend this policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, as determined by Epilog Laser, in the way in which Personal Information is collected, used, or transferred, we will notify you of these changes by modification of this Privacy Policy, which will be available for review by you at the Services. Notwithstanding any modifications we may make, any Personal Information collected by Epilog Laser from you will be treated in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time information was collected, unless we obtain your consent otherwise.

_Children:_

Epilog Laser does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and the Services may only be used by persons under 13 years of age under the supervision of a school, parent, guardian, or teacher. If Epilog Laser learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been provided, then Epilog Laser will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. To request that such information be deleted, contact us at [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com).

**Geographic Location**

We offer the Services in several geographic regions. We define a geographic region as the location where a user is located.

_Users in Regions Other Than the European Union:_

For users located outside of the European Union, we process data with third party data processors and handlers located in the United States and Canada. We have adopted reasonable physical, technical, and organizational safeguards against accidental, unauthorized, or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use, or processing of user data in our possession. We comply with state and federal laws governing the protection of personal information.

_Users Within the European Union:_

For users located within the European Union, we transfer data for processing from the European Union to third party data processors and handlers located in the United States and Canada. Such processing is performed in accordance with Regulation 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). This includes the imposition of required safeguards with respect to accidental, unauthorized, or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of data. Transfers of European Union user data to processors in the United States and Canada are made in accordance with the GDPR.

**Retention and Deletion**

We will only retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and processed, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, accounting, or reporting requirements. If you would like your Personal Information to be deleted prior to the date that it would normally be deleted in the ordinary course of Epilog Laser’s business, please let us know at [privacy@epiloglaser.com](mailto:privacy@epiloglaser.com) and we will promptly comply.

**About Us**

We are based in the United States of America at 16371 Table Mountain Parkway, Golden, Colorado 80403. Users in the United States and regions other than the European Union can contact us at the above address.

Our representative in the EU for GDPR purposes is Epilog Laser BV. You can contact our representative at Duwboot 1, 3991 CD Houten, Nederland.

Effective date of this policy: May 25, 2018

### Popular Pages
